– So, hello. My name is Fervil O'Connor.
I'm the Identity Solutions Lead Architects
at the KERON Foundation. Over the last few
years, I've been helping build out the
open source identity solution known as
Beredium. Today, I gave a talk on the
KERIA and Signify TS security
architecture. So, we delved into
operationally how KERIA works to be a
cloud agent in… I should go back there. We
delved into how KERIA and Signify TS can
enable stateless signing at the edge both
operationally, we delved into some
architecture diagrams, and also from a
trust relationship point of view, delved
into which keys to the where, who signs
what, and so forth, and how you can use
KERIA and Signify to interact with the
entire world. I think one thing that we do
differently is, you know, crunch. We're
trying to bring KERIA to the masses. It's
essentially a set of cybersecurity
protocols that are very low level. What
I've been trying to do with KERIA is to
take low level KERIA and make it
accessible to, you know, individuals and
organizations alike in a way that's super
streamlined and highly accessible. I think
my talk today on KERIA and Signify kind of
relates to that in the sense that Signify
can provide a higher level API to
developers as more accessible. Yeah, I
mean, if KERIA and Signify were to
disappear, you know, everything we're
doing is built on open protocols. You
don't have open protocols. You don't have
any lock-in to particular software stacks.
You know, I'm sure the community would
find other ways and there already are
existing other ways to create your KERIA
identifiers, interact with the world. This
is just one particular implementation and
one flavor of that. And so if it
disappears, you know, we would see
different flavors popping up from
different organizations and different open
source communities. This is how sovereign
at the end of the day.